Backstab;If sneak skill checks, double Melee CM
Alchemist;Create single use spell potion per heroism spent
Rage;1 HP increment cost gets +1 All CM and -1 All D for encounter
Artificer;Imbue (use) heroism onto gemstone at gem level (gold / 100) charges
Turn Undead;Lower all undead defenses by 3 for 5 rounds per encounter
Inspire;Allies get one extra heroism roll per level
Telepathy;Willing two way mind link, MIND Score distance
Cleanse;Remove all rounds from a single effect, from one target, once per encounter (touch)
Magic Synergies;Add 2 points to a single spell per encounter