Backstab;If sneak skill checks, add Sub to CM
Rage;4 HP increment cost gets +4 CM and -2 AC for encounter
Martial Arts;Magic Fists [1d8] + (1/2 lvl) CM + (1/2 lvl + 1) AC
Artifice;Imbue Heroism onto gemstone at 2d6 charges + gem level
Inspire;Allies get one free heroism roll per combat
Turn Undead;HP is DC, over DC (Fear), +10 over DC destroy
Lay on Hands;Heal up to 2 hp per level per heroism spent
Magic Synergies;Heal 2 hp per round in combat of magic cost damage
Combat Training;Gain (1/5 lvl) CM to all weapons
Well Rounded;+2 to Lowest Stat
Talented;+2 to Lowest Skill
Disguise;Change Appearance at will @ 1d6 dmg
Telepathy;Two way mind link at will, MIND Score ft.