The Girl with Many Faces
A PC's longtime paramour comes to a second PC and  reveals itself as a doppelganger
 It admits that it was given instruction in proper behavior by the first PC's original lover, who had slowly come to loathe the PC and was actually milking her for intelligence to send to the party's enemies
 The doppelganger took over for the lover and continued spying on the party, but it has now fallen in love with the second PC, doesn't want to betray the party anymore, and hopes that its honesty is proof of the sincerity of its feelings

If allowed to prove its loyalty, the former spy will be willing to not only stop its illicit activities but also to feed false information to its employers or counter-spy for the PCs
 This may prove a valuable source of information for the party, especially if stealthy characters are willing to accompany their double agent to meetings

This plot is likely to cause some difficult emotional times for the PCs-and to spark some good roleplaying
 Other factors can make the situation more difficult: The doppelganger might prove overeager to please its new lover, for example, making quicksilver changes to its features, gender, and attitudes to match anyone who piques the PC's interest

Once the doppelganger drops its old form, an old friend it had been maintaining contact with as part of its cover becomes suspicious about its sudden disappearance
 Convinced that the doppelganger's lover-the original, betrayed PC-has engaged in foul play, he confronts the party
 Without a satisfying explanation, the old friend will report the disappearance to the authorities

Eventually the doppelganger's employers discover that it's a double agent, or simply decide that the recent decrease in the quality of information makes it more valuable as an example than a spy
 Either way, the PCs will have to defend their new friend against would-be assassins

Alternately, the entire situation could be a carefully engineered plot for some purpose not readily apparent
 If the doppelganger is indeed a false double agent, the whole scheme must have been put in motion in anticipation of an exceptionally large payoff

While the younger dragons explore the world, their elders fight to keep their order alive at home. The elder and ancient dragons of the Chamber include accomplished prophets and loredrakes, and their insights into the Prophecy have helped to mollify the great powers of Argonnessen about the wisdom of their interfence with the humanoid races. But it is an ongoing struggle, with no rest for the wise. The Conclave of Argonessen When the dragons first gathered to plot their rebellion against the fiends who controlled the world in the Age of Demons, it was the eldest among them who laid out their plans. This tradition continues to the present day. 


Name           : Neva Ambrose, "The Red Sash"
Level          : 3
Title          : Vengeful Folk Hero
Race           : Human
Class          : Artificer
Attack         : Scimitar (1d6+6) or Light Crossbow 80 ft (1d8+4)
Vitals         : HP: 40, AC: 16
Stats          : StrMod: 3, DexMod: 1, MindMod: 2, | Phys: 4, Sub: 4, Know: 6, Comm: 4, Surv: 4
Quote          : You serve an unjust king. Now, forfeit your purse or forfeit your life.
Appearance     : The Red Sash's costume consists of a black tricorn hat, hair tucked into a headscarf mask, satin 
                 blouse, trousers, overcoat, and riding boots. Clad in black from head to foot, save for a red sash 
                 holding a rapier at her waist, she stands in profile-mysterious and forbidding. Otherwise, Neva is 
                 plain-looking and wears a serving-girl's apron.
Roleplaying    : The Red Sash speaks as little as possible, and uses a low, rasping voice as part of her disguise.
Personality    : She cares little for her rising status as a folk hero. Songs and stories of her exploits are well and 
                 good, but her appetite is for revenge. She's not doing this to lead an uprising, but she's beginning 
                 to realize that she'll need allies.
Motivation     : Neva wants repayment for the crown's injustice in blood.
Background     : She already had no love for the crown because of the stiff taxes placed on the neighborhood 
                 businesses, including her father's tavern. But she swore her revenge when her young beau was drafted 
                 into the king's service and died under the command of some foppish gentleman who ordered him on an 
                 unwarranted adventure. Now she rides the King's Road, exacting a bloody toll on agents of the crown. 
                 She periodically switches mounts, so she can't be identified by her horse.
Traits         : Mysterious, notorious, stealthy
CharacterSheet : CharacterSheet
GameNotes      : 

Level         : 3
ClassInternal : CharacterClass
RaceInternal  : CharacterRace
STR           : 18
DEX           : 12
MIND          : 15
MeleeCM       : 6
RangedCM      : 4
MeleeType     : Scimitar
MeleeDamage   : 1d6
RangedType    : Light Crossbow 80 ft
RangedDamage  : 1d8
ArmorAC       : 5
Race          : Human
Class         : Artificer
AC            : 16
HP            : 40
SpellDC       : 15
Attack        : Scimitar (1d6+6) or Light Crossbow 80 ft (1d8+4)
StrMod        : 3
DexMod        : 1
MindMod       : 2
ArmorType     : Breastplate
Phys          : 4
Sub           : 4
Know          : 6
Comm          : 4
Surv          : 4
Traits        : NA and Can imbue an appropriate 'Heroism Type' onto a gemstone with 1d12 charges + gem level
Description   : NA and NA

Name           : Duke Merkton
Level          : 3
Title          : Religious Laborer
Race           : Half-Elf
Class          : Paladin
Attack         : Guisarme (2d4+4) or Dart 20 ft (1d4+5)
Vitals         : HP: 39, AC: 19
Stats          : StrMod: 1, DexMod: 2, MindMod: 2, | Phys: 3, Sub: 3, Know: 3, Comm: 6, Surv: 3
Quote          : Wealth can kill a man, but hard work will keep him strong.
Appearance     : The duke is a man creeping into his elder years. He is bald with a large thick mustache. He rarely 
                 wears his royal attire, and prefers work clothes.
Roleplaying    : He listens more than he speaks, and when he does speak, he is a bit vague. This helps him to avoid 
                 obligations that are not aligned with his motives.
Personality    : He is easily annoyed by people or things that keep him from his work as a master stonemason. He 
                 respects the responsibilities that come with his title, but he avoids frivolous events such as royal 
                 balls and ceremonies whenever possible. Religious ceremonies are an exception, as he is a man of 
                 great faith and devotion.
Motivation     : Duke Merkton believes that by building roads, temples, mills, and other structures needed by his 
                 people, he is fulfilling his obligation to the gods. He does not merely design the structures, 
                 though, as he is hands-on with every project-shaping the stones alongside his workers.
Background     : The young duke was a drunk exploiting his great wealth. He fell ill due to his heavy drinking, and 
                 his father threw him into a labor camp to correct his attitude and behavior. There, he learned how to 
                 shape stones, how to love the holy texts, and the connection between them. The duke emerged from the 
                 camp as a man devoted to both his craft and his faith.
Traits         : Laborer, religious, royalty, wealthy
CharacterSheet : CharacterSheet
GameNotes      : 

Level         : 3
ClassInternal : CharacterClass
RaceInternal  : CharacterRace
STR           : 13
DEX           : 15
MIND          : 14
MeleeCM       : 4
RangedCM      : 5
MeleeType     : Guisarme
MeleeDamage   : 2d4
RangedType    : Dart 20 ft
RangedDamage  : 1d4
ArmorAC       : 7
Race          : Half-Elf
Class         : Paladin
AC            : 19
HP            : 39
SpellDC       : 15
Attack        : Guisarme (2d4+4) or Dart 20 ft (1d4+5)
StrMod        : 1
DexMod        : 2
MindMod       : 2
ArmorType     : Half-Plate
Phys          : 3
Sub           : 3
Know          : 3
Comm          : 6
Surv          : 3
Traits        : +2 to Heroism Roles and Their touch and melee attacks may cure (not self) or inflict 2 HP on allies or 
                evil enemies for every 1 HP they exhaust (d20+4 must be above AC on CM roll). May cast Divine spells 
                with a spell level equal to or below Â¼ caster level (round down)
Description   : NA and NA

Name           : Lana the Peace Bringer
Level          : 6
Title          : Deluded Crime Lord
Race           : Half-Elf
Class          : Rogues
Attack         : Light Hammer (1d6+10) or Javelin 30 ft (1d6+8)
Vitals         : HP: 52, AC: 15
Stats          : StrMod: 4, DexMod: 2, MindMod: -1, | Phys: 6, Sub: 9, Know: 6, Comm: 6, Surv: 6
Quote          : War is death. Violence is pain. Renounce such ways and follow me. It isn't as if you have a choice.
Appearance     : She is tall and buxom with brilliant red hair and emerald green eyes. Her ivory skin is complimented 
                 by a fur cloak and bronze armor. She carries a matching bronze spear.
Roleplaying    : She speaks kindly to people until they dare question her. When confronted, she will verbally or even 
                 physically assault her perceived adversary.
Personality    : Lana is warm with words but cold in actions. She promises to lead people to a better life, but is 
                 oblivious to how she hurts others. She has no tolerance for anyone who opposes her or her 
                 organization.
Motivation     : Lana is a crime lord with delusions of grandeur. She wants love from those she protects; if they 
                 don't love her, she will kill them.
Background     : Lana's father was a notorious crime lord, but wanted a better, more honest life for her. She was sent 
                 to the finest academies and excelled in all subjects. Upon returning home, she learned her father had 
                 been assassinated by a rival. With her father's passion and the knowledge afforded by her schooling, 
                 Lana easily took control of the organization and eliminated her competitors. In her mind, she had 
                 delivered peace. She realized there were many territories that needed "protection." Fooled by her own 
                 lies, what she began for revenge and continued for profit has become a self-righteous crusade.
Traits         : Beautiful, criminal, scholar
CharacterSheet : CharacterSheet
GameNotes      : 

Level         : 6
ClassInternal : CharacterClass
RaceInternal  : CharacterRace
STR           : 19
DEX           : 15
MIND          : 8
MeleeCM       : 10
RangedCM      : 8
MeleeType     : Light Hammer
MeleeDamage   : 1d6
RangedType    : Javelin 30 ft
RangedDamage  : 1d6
ArmorAC       : 3
Race          : Half-Elf
Class         : Rogues
AC            : 15
HP            : 52
SpellDC       : 15
Attack        : Light Hammer (1d6+10) or Javelin 30 ft (1d6+8)
StrMod        : 4
DexMod        : 2
MindMod       : -1
ArmorType     : Hide
Phys          : 6
Sub           : 9
Know          : 6
Comm          : 6
Surv          : 6
Traits        : +2 to Heroism Roles and If they successfully Sneak (usually sub+DEX but depends on situation) up on a 
                foe they can add their Subterfuge skill rank to the damage of their first attack
Description   : NA and NA




CR Name    Type                 HP AC DamageCM                      Speed        
-- ----    ----                 -- -- --------                      -----        
 7 BULETTE Huge Magical Beast   94 22 Bite: 2d8+24, 2 Claws: 2d6+14 8/ 2 (burrow)
 2 WORG    Medium Magical Beast 30 14 Bite: 1d6+11 &Trip            10           




Name           : BULETTE
Image          : E:\Other\PS_Scripts\Personal\DnDMicroliteTools\Data\Images\BULETTE.jpg
SpecialAttacks : Leap - may make 4 claw attacks
Notes          : This armor-plated creature's toothy maw gapes wide as a fin-like dorsal plate rises between its 
                 shoulders. Also known as the landshark, the Bulette is a terrifying predator that lives only to eat. 

Name           : WORG
Image          : E:\Other\PS_Scripts\Personal\DnDMicroliteTools\Data\Images\WORG.jpg
SpecialAttacks : Trip - If bite attack hits may trip +3
Notes          : More intelligent than their smaller cousins, the wolf, a Worg has gray or black fur, grows to 5 feet 
                 long and stands 3 feet tall at the shoulder. It weighs 300 pounds. 




Level Name   Race       Class     Vitals         Attack                                                
----- ----   ----       -----     ------         ------                                                
    2 Ovix   Changeling Fighter   HP: 26, AC: 15 Greatsword (2d6+4) or Javelin 30 ft (1d6+3)           
    3 Ceroi  Half-Elf   Cleric    HP: 35, AC: 21 Heavy Flail (1d10+4) or Heavy Crossbow 120 ft (1d10+6)
    3 Ilian  Human      Artificer HP: 46, AC: 18 Spear (1d8+7) or Light Crossbow 80 ft (1d8+5)         
    4 Thorhe Dwarf      Rogues    HP: 50, AC: 18 Guisarme (2d4+7) or Shortbow 60 ft (1d6+6)            




Name       : Ovix
Appearance : Ovix is tall, with gray hair and bright gray eyes
Traits     : Ovix has an animal companion, a hunting dog named Mida.

Name       : Ceroi
Appearance : Ceroi has braided copper hair and amber eyes, and a round nose
Traits     : 

Name       : Ilian
Appearance : Ilian is tall and thin, with copper hair and large amber eyes
Traits     : Ilian is easily distracted by food and drink.

Name       : Thorhe
Appearance : Thorhe has red hair and bright gray eyes
Traits     : Thorhe suffers a paralyzing fear of mirrors.



