

DiceNumber : 30
Gold       : 86
Items      : {Shortsword of Brilliance + 1, Heavy Crossbow}

DiceNumber : 31
Gold       : 86
Items      : {Banded eye agate (10 gp)}

DiceNumber : 32
Gold       : 92
Items      : {}

DiceNumber : 33
Gold       : 100
Items      : {Chain Shirt of Heroism + 1, Average Lock}

DiceNumber : 34
Gold       : 90
Items      : {Padded Leather of Hunting + 1, Greatsword, azurite (10 gp)}

DiceNumber : 35
Gold       : 96
Items      : {}

DiceNumber : 36
Gold       : 87
Items      : {Spear}

DiceNumber : 37
Gold       : 94
Items      : {}

DiceNumber : 38
Gold       : 91
Items      : {Splint Mail of Tongues + 1, Fine Gold Bracelet (90 gp)}

DiceNumber : 39
Gold       : 89
Items      : {Breastplate of Brilliance + 1, Buckler, hematite (15 gp)}

DiceNumber : 40
Gold       : 92
Items      : {Everburning torch of Hardening + 1, Masterwork Manacles, Cloth of Gold Vestments (130 gp)}

DiceNumber : 41
Gold       : 95
Items      : {Heavy Wooden Shield, azurite (8 gp), Carved Bone Statuette (30 gp)}

DiceNumber : 42
Gold       : 98
Items      : {Heavy Crossbow}

DiceNumber : 43
Gold       : 86
Items      : {Banded eye agate (9 gp), Cloth of Gold Vestments (120 gp)}

DiceNumber : 44
Gold       : 98
Items      : {Full Plate, rhodochrosite (9 gp)}

DiceNumber : 45
Gold       : 94
Items      : {Half-Plate of Gutting + 1, Chainmail, lapis lazuli (9 gp)}

DiceNumber : 46
Gold       : 177
Items      : {Light Steel Shield, azurite (6 gp), Silver Chalice with Lapis Lazuli Gems (120 gp)}

DiceNumber : 47
Gold       : 199
Items      : {Scroll Case, Banded eye agate (9 gp), Silver Chalice with Lapis Lazuli Gems (130 gp)}

DiceNumber : 48
Gold       : 189
Items      : {Longspear, obsidian (9 gp), Black Velvet Mask with Citrines (130 gp)}

DiceNumber : 49
Gold       : 192
Items      : {Padded Leather, Fine Gold Bracelet (60 gp)}

DiceNumber : 50
Gold       : 98
Items      : {Empty Backpack, Cloth of Gold Vestments (80 gp)}

DiceNumber : 51
Gold       : 86
Items      : {Light Pickaxe of Endurance + 1, Tanglefoot bags (1d4 bags)}

DiceNumber : 52
Gold       : 192
Items      : {Masterwork Manacles of Hunting + 1, Silver Chalice with Lapis Lazuli Gems (60 gp)}

DiceNumber : 53
Gold       : 191
Items      : {Heavy Wooden Shield, tiger eye turquoise (9 gp), Black Velvet Mask with Citrines (120 gp)}

DiceNumber : 54
Gold       : 85
Items      : {Scroll of Shadow + 1, Leather, moss agate (7 gp)}

DiceNumber : 55
Gold       : 183
Items      : {Healing Potion (STR Score + lvl), malachite (12 gp)}

DiceNumber : 56
Gold       : 98
Items      : {Scroll of Endurance + 1, tiger eye turquoise (5 gp), Cloth of Gold Vestments (130 gp)}

DiceNumber : 57
Gold       : 181
Items      : {Greataxe of Tongues + 1, Shortsword, tiger eye turquoise (6 gp)}

DiceNumber : 58
Gold       : 181
Items      : {Full Plate}

DiceNumber : 59
Gold       : 171
Items      : {Smokesticks (1d4 sticks), Cloth of Gold Vestments (100 gp)}

DiceNumber : 60
Gold       : 91
Items      : {Chainmail, azurite (7 gp)}

DiceNumber : 61
Gold       : 92
Items      : {Scythe of Power + 1, irregular pearl (10 gp), Silver Chalice with Lapis Lazuli Gems (90 gp)}

DiceNumber : 62
Gold       : 93
Items      : {Amulet of Brilliance + 1, blue quartz (9 gp), Black Velvet Mask with Citrines (100 gp)}

DiceNumber : 63
Gold       : 178
Items      : {Chainmail of Wisdom + 1, Greatclub, lapis lazuli (11 gp), Carved Bone Statuette (100 gp)}

DiceNumber : 64
Gold       : 194
Items      : {Breastplate of Tongues + 1, Morningstar}

DiceNumber : 65
Gold       : 172
Items      : {Longsword of Hunting + 1, Piton, obsidian (6 gp), Silver Ewer (50 gp)}

DiceNumber : 66
Gold       : 181
Items      : {Hide Armor, azurite (8 gp), Fine Gold Bracelet (90 gp)}

DiceNumber : 67
Gold       : 173
Items      : {Scimitar of Brilliance + 1, Silver Chalice with Lapis Lazuli Gems (120 gp)}

DiceNumber : 68
Gold       : 95
Items      : {Dart of Endurance + 1, Scythe, Cloth of Gold Vestments (110 gp)}

DiceNumber : 69
Gold       : 88
Items      : {Ring of Endurance + 1, blue quartz (10 gp), Ivory Statuette (80 gp)}

DiceNumber : 70
Gold       : 180
Items      : {Padded Leather}

DiceNumber : 71
Gold       : 90
Items      : {Simple Lock, obsidian (10 gp), Fine Gold Bracelet (40 gp)}

DiceNumber : 72
Gold       : 186
Items      : {Trident, moss agate (12 gp), Ivory Statuette (80 gp)}

DiceNumber : 73
Gold       : 200
Items      : {Padded Leather, rhodochrosite (13 gp), Carved Bone Statuette (100 gp)}

DiceNumber : 74
Gold       : 192
Items      : {Splint Mail of Tongues + 1, Glaive, Silver Chalice with Lapis Lazuli Gems (120 gp)}

DiceNumber : 75
Gold       : 382
Items      : {Scythe, Black Velvet Mask with Citrines (140 gp)}

DiceNumber : 76
Gold       : 190
Items      : {Halberd, Ivory Statuette (90 gp)}

DiceNumber : 77
Gold       : 177
Items      : {Healing Potion (STR Score + lvl), lapis lazuli (11 gp)}

DiceNumber : 78
Gold       : 194
Items      : {Buckler of Endurance + 2, Empty Backpack, tiger eye turquoise (7 gp)}

DiceNumber : 79
Gold       : 376
Items      : {Simple Lock of Endurance + 2, Light Wooden Shield, moss agate (11 gp), Cloth of Gold Vestments (100 gp)}

DiceNumber : 80
Gold       : 347
Items      : {Chainmail}

DiceNumber : 81
Gold       : 182
Items      : {Heavy Crossbow of Brilliance + 2, Trident, irregular pearl (14 gp), Silver Chalice with Lapis Lazuli 
             Gems (80 gp)}

DiceNumber : 82
Gold       : 183
Items      : {Buckler of Hardening + 2, tiger eye turquoise (15 gp), Black Velvet Mask with Citrines (70 gp)}

DiceNumber : 83
Gold       : 181
Items      : {Padded Leather of Power + 2, Banded eye agate (9 gp), Silver Chalice with Lapis Lazuli Gems (120 gp)}

DiceNumber : 84
Gold       : 385
Items      : {Leather, lapis lazuli (11 gp)}

DiceNumber : 85
Gold       : 384
Items      : {Scroll of Wisdom + 2, Banded Mail, blue quartz (9 gp)}

DiceNumber : 86
Gold       : 345
Items      : {Thieves' tools of Hardening + 2, Caltrops, Ivory Statuette (100 gp)}

DiceNumber : 87
Gold       : 395
Items      : {Shortsword of Gutting + 2, Splint Mail, Ivory Statuette (30 gp)}

DiceNumber : 88
Gold       : 378
Items      : {Masterwork Manacles, azurite (6 gp)}

DiceNumber : 89
Gold       : 396
Items      : {hematite (13 gp)}

DiceNumber : 90
Gold       : 177
Items      : {Light Wooden Shield, moss agate (10 gp), Silver Ewer (20 gp)}

DiceNumber : 91
Gold       : 175
Items      : {Holy water (1d4 flasks) of Hunting + 2, Sling, Fine Gold Bracelet (60 gp)}

DiceNumber : 92
Gold       : 583
Items      : {Scroll of Power + 2, Empty Backpack, Banded eye agate (11 gp), Silver Chalice with Lapis Lazuli Gems (70 
             gp)}

DiceNumber : 93
Gold       : 543
Items      : {Sickle of Heroism + 2, Everburning torch, azurite (7 gp), Ivory Statuette (50 gp)}

DiceNumber : 94
Gold       : 593
Items      : {Scroll of Endurance + 2, Piton, rhodochrosite (8 gp), Ivory Statuette (60 gp)}

DiceNumber : 95
Gold       : 584
Items      : {Scale Mail, hematite (12 gp), Silver Chalice with Lapis Lazuli Gems (110 gp)}

DiceNumber : 96
Gold       : 385
Items      : {Scythe of Power + 2, Light Wooden Shield, blue quartz (13 gp)}

DiceNumber : 97
Gold       : 543
Items      : {Scroll of Hunting + 2, Glaive, tiger eye turquoise (12 gp), Silver Chalice with Lapis Lazuli Gems (100 
             gp)}

DiceNumber : 98
Gold       : 361
Items      : {Morningstar, hematite (10 gp)}

DiceNumber : 99
Gold       : 556
Items      : {Full Plate of Hardening + 2, Chain Shirt, hematite (12 gp)}

DiceNumber : 100
Gold       : 357
Items      : {Amulet of Brilliance + 2, Sickle, Fine Gold Bracelet (20 gp)}





NameType : human
Names    : {Forthven , Via'vin , Ri-ca , Sha'cynwig ...}

NameType : elf
Names    : {Rithand , Themíte , Thressaim , Sha'moril ...}

NameType : dwarf
Names    : {Thigraki , Duumhjalror , The'fals , Kjaldasha ...}

NameType : hobbit
Names    : {Lothoama Fairwhit , Liman Hay-hand , Topo Bairnblower , Ranard Hornwhit ...}

NameType : barbarian
Names    : {Cwen-gund , Hallri , Axewolfthak , Aecroethel ...}

NameType : orc
Names    : {Snarl-ong , Orumeg , Grobrukdal , Bolgga ...}

NameType : evil
Names    : {Ardnazgbo , Thadraxbeelver , Cutaresh , Musryma ...}

NameType : asian
Names    : {Thaiparkshi , Lamro , Tsuchankhanyang , Yingdora ...}

NameType : arabic
Names    : {Murasra , Fafiha , Naya'lah , Sa-la ...}

NameType : surnames
Names    : {Breakpickersummer , Longsunrage , Sunmoorsteel , Flamehelmnight ...}

NameType : sf
Names    : {Naruzoq , Palposu , Roon-ta , Po'ren ...}

NameType : lovecraft
Names    : {Korongoth , N'thlic'ba , Cthunothroth , Tlaglnthog ...}

NameType : reptilian
Names    : {Ssiythatys , Otlhysssat , Sensassa , Seshsiyss ...}

NameType : aztec
Names    : {Licolpalnoy , Chitlquinal , Cocoa , Caeciya ...}

NameType : ratman
Names    : {Assik-vi , Kikiecchi , Nikgazneth , Assiktavfe ...}

NameType : demon
Names    : {Nemtis , Nio've , Apcurobe , Mal-o ...}

NameType : dragon
Names    : {De'yazri , Mon-horn , Da'im , Gon'a ...}

NameType : wizard
Names    : {Lezumrin , Nyl-zo , Do-nus , Rulanea ...}

NameType : mixed
Names    : {Modinmo , Marraeviok , Debarlak , Istthdaluk ...}

NameType : enames
Names    : {Gina Maria Rye , Drea Dane Hull }

NameType : places
Names    : {Valley of Cards , Annadelnathville , Mount Worm , Mount Bottle ...}

NameType : titles
Names    : {<name>  the Ward , <name>  the Nasty , <name>  the Shade , <name>  the Canny ...}

NameType : super
Names    : {Card Fox , Veil Man , Captain Minute , Lord Foible ...}

NameType : rockband
Names    : {The Broken Chair , Slick Insane Room , Adele's Quitter , The Curved Law ...}




Name      
----      
Narath    
Stormreach
Sylbaran  
          
          
          
          
          
          




Name  : alien-descriptions
Value : {0, These aliens are a type of invertebrate. They have four clawed arms and two legs, with a long, useless 
        tail.
        
        They have four eyes which sit graciously in their sockets and can often make them appear to be friendly. Their 
        eyesight is fairly good.
        
        Their narrow mouths and almost hidden noses often make these aliens appear to be nervous, but looks can be 
        deceiving.
        Their ears are will hidden and their hearing is not too great at distances. They also have horns running 
        across their backs.
        
        Their skin is smooth and thin. It's covered short hairs.
        Their skin colors are mostly dark brown, light blue, black and yellow, which tend to become pale as they age.
        
        The males are usually heavier than their female counter part and their colors are less vibrant. The females, 
        however, are usually more emotional.}

Name  : animal-descriptions
Value : {0, This bizarre, but fairly common creature is a type of mammal. It's about the size of a rat, has six legs, 
        but they have no tail.
        They have a soft, smooth skin covered in thick, fluffy fur which is usually either silver, dark silver or 
        light grey or a combination of these colors.
        
        They live in snowy areas and are fairly rare. They're omnivores and their fairly small mouths, their teeth and 
        rough tongue are ideal for eating grasses.
        
        They're crepuscular and rely on their sense of smell and hearing to get around. They do have large, elliptic 
        eyes, but their sight is not very reliable.
        They have huge noses and tiny, almost hidden ears. Their heads are long and narrow in comparison to their 
        bodies.
        
        They make sounds ranging from very high pitched to low pitched and have a fairly small range of sounds they 
        make to indicate discoveries, dangers and otherwise communicate with each other.
        
        These creatures are very timid, but they're quite territorial. They mate twice a year and they mate with a 
        select group of partners for life. Which, with their long lifepans, is quite common among other species as 
        well.}

Name  : leather-armor-descriptions
Value : {0, This set of armor has a rounded helm with two small metal plates at each side of the eyes to protect the 
        face. Attached to the top is a large leather crafted wing-shaped ornament, curving across the top and towards 
        the back.
        The shoulders are fairly rounded, very wide and huge. They're decorated with hundreds of small leather pieces, 
        mimicking the scales of reptiles.
        
        The upper arms are protected by pointed, half covering rerebraces which sit quite well under the 
        shoulderplates. The lower arms are covered by vambraces which have a masterfully crafted leather snake curling 
        around them.
        
        The breastplate is made from many layers of smaller leather pieces, mimicking the scales of a reptile. It 
        covers only the front, the back is where the attachment straps are and they offer no real protection.
        
        The upper legs are covered by rounded, half covering cuisses. The lower legs are protected by leather greaves 
        which have several metal rings attached to the outer sides. Thin leather pants are worn beneath this all.}

Name  : plate-armor-descriptions
Value : {0, This set of armor has a squared helm with half a face guard shaped like the eyes of a dragon. Attached to 
        the forehead area is a broken animal horn.
        The shoulders are fairly pointy, short and huge. They're decorated with masterfully crafted metal hands on 
        each side.
        
        The upper arms are protected by pointed, half covering rerebraces which sit well under the shoulderplates. The 
        lower arms are covered by vambraces which have a large sharkfin-like spike attached to each outer side.
        
        The breastplate is made from one large piece of metal, but crafted to mimic the appearance of muscles. It 
        covers the entire front and back side, but the attachment straps leave the sides under the arms exposed.
        
        The upper legs are covered by squared, fully covering cuisses. The lower legs are protected by greaves which 
        have several rows of barb-like spikes on the outer sides.}

Name  : army-descriptions
Value : {0, The ground trembles as an army of 150,000 marches as one. Thousands of feet trample the ground beneath it, 
        drowning out all other sound from the vicinity.
        
        Up close it's the rustling of chainmail and leather which overpowers all other sounds. The creaking of metal 
        of the siege engines can be heard only faintly and the growls of the war hounds are all but drowned out 
        completely.
        The soldiers are talking amongst themselves despite the noise around them. Some need it to take their minds of 
        the battle ahead, some need it to hype themselves up for it. The army is a mismatch of isolated groups, but 
        they'll work together as they share the same goal: Destroy the enemy and make it back home.
        
        The front is lead by eager bowmen with incredible range. They're followed by cavalry armed with several 
        swords, who in turn are followed by elite footsoldiers armed with pikes.
        The ranks are filled with many other regiments, including allied soldiers, as well as slave soldiers, 
        including various flanking units, various charging units, several bomb units and many elite units.}

Name  : backstory-descriptions
Value : {0, He's driven, mysterious, faithful and perhaps a little too confused. But there's more than meets the eye, 
        not surprising for somebody with his position.
        
        He was born in a royal family in a large port. He lived in peace until he was about 15 years old, but at that 
        point life changed.
        
        He started to experience the world and was very successful. After an astonishing adventure, he is trying to 
        reach the top in a fast changing world. But with his persistence and brilliance, there's nothing to stop him 
        from improving the world. He could quickly become an unstoppable force.
        
        But there may be more to it than this; he is currently still studying. He feels like there's more incredible 
        sights to behold in this world. Luckily he has plenty of resources to support him.}

Name  : battlefield-descriptions
Value : {0, The field is littered with weapons, suits and shells. Red, gray and pink are the new colors of what was 
        once a delicate, snowy field, which has now become the stage of a long, destructive battle.
        The air which would normally be delicate and quiet is now glowing red with fire and thick with smoke, ash and 
        embers, enough to destroy whatever courage is left in the survivors.
        
        Two parties fight each other due to a difference in beliefs, but at this point it's undeniable which side will 
        win. The dead and wounded of the losing side lay in heaps across the field and the faces of the fighters are 
        grim with the certainty of death and sorrow, but they refuse to give up.
        
        With the thought of victory in their minds the winning side fights as if they're invinsible. Some have 
        succumbed to bloodlust and are recklessly charging towards the enemy with only the aim to kill all, while 
        others long for the end of this battle.
        
        The toll on both nature and humanity is unimaginable. It'll likely take ages before this field will have 
        recovered. It's clear debris, metal and gore have taken the place of shrubs, plants and bushes.}

Name  : castle-descriptions
Value : {0, Thirteen thin, square towers surround the castle in almost a perfect circle around this incredible castle 
        and are connected by towering, firm walls made of basalt.
        Tall windows are scattered thinly around the walls in seeminly perfect symmetry, along with overhanging 
        crenelations for archers and artillery.
        
        A moderate gate with hefty wooden doors, a regular bridge and a moat protects those in need of aid in this 
        rough mountain pass, but it's not the only way in, which fortunately only very few know.
        
        Lush fields of crops surround the castle walls and provides the inhabitants with food all year round. This 
        castle has clearly been around for at least a thousand years, but it doesn't seem like it will collapse any 
        time soon.}

Name  : character-descriptions
Value : {0, White, short hair gently hangs over a skinny, warm face. Bright amber eyes, set charmingly within their 
        sockets, watch loyally over the mountains they've grieved with for so long.
        A large beard elegantly compliments his hair and cheekbones and leaves a heartbreaking memory of his former 
        lovers.
        
        This is the face of Kade Eustice, a true mercenary among humans. He stands common among others, despite his 
        bulky frame.
        
        There's something puzzling about him, perhaps it's his persistence or perhaps it's simply his gentleness. But 
        nonetheless, people tend to ask him to tell stories, while trying to subtly look more like him.}

Name  : city-descriptions
Value : {0, The city of Shroudmoor was built at the border of a traitorous jungle and is truly a contemporary display 
        of wonder. Its charm is matched by the backdrop of gentle hills which have helped shape the city to what it is 
        today.
        The climate these hills brought were of great importance, but they were also influential when it came to 
        architectural designs as the vast majority of buildings have been built with many round shapes and wide sizes, 
        similar to the fields around them.
        
        The skyline is sprinkled with elegant skyscrapers and they each represent the many different aspects of the 
        city. Health and services are faultless in Shroudmoor and it has attracted a lot of attention. Countless 
        cultures have left their mark not just on the architecture, but also upon the city's identity. What 
        historically was a city of predictability has grown into a multicultural hub and it's this that unites the 14 
        million people to this day.
        
        It's this multicultural identity that has truly left its mark. Hundreds of food carts, bars and take-outs 
        offer a plethora of culinary choices and those who feel hungry for something else can enjoy city exploring, 
        water sports, concerts or one of the many other recreational venues.}

Name  : fancy-clothing-descriptions
Value : {0, The dress covers her shoulders only barely with 2 spaghetti straps and flows down into a simple jewel 
        neckline. It's a comfortable fit which makes the dress both enjoyable to wear and look at.
        Her arms have been covered to just below her elbows. The sleeves are a loose fit and, in a way, help put focus 
        on her soft skin.
        
        The dress' waist is thin, but it's a comfortable fit. A bow has been wrapped around her and rests gently on 
        her belly.
        Below the waist the dress fits snug around her and has a tulip style. The dress reaches all the way down, 
        almost covering her feet and is the same length all around.
        
        She's wearing slingbacks, a perfect choice in combination with this dress. To top it all off she's wearing a 
        simple, but stylish necklace and small jeweled earrings.}

Name  : medieval-clothing-descriptions
Value : {0, His fairly long sleeved, leather jacket covers him to just above his knees and is loosely tied with string 
        at the left side. The sleeves of his jacket are a little narrow and reach down to well below his wrists, 
        they're decorated with a single thread lining and a decorative band.
        
        The jacket has a narrow, rectangular neckline which reveals part of the majestic shirt worn below it and is 
        worn with a thin cloth band, which is held together by a small belt buckle. The cloth band is almost entirely 
        a functional addition.
        
        His pants are simple and quite wide and reach down to his hard leather shoes. The shoes are made from a very 
        rare leather, but are otherwise not that special.}

Name  : rag-clothing-descriptions
Value : {0, What was once a shirt is now nothing more than dirty pieces of fabric barely held together, hanging from 
        his shoulders like a discarded old towel.
        There's a huge hole in one of the shoulders which reaches almost all the way down, leaving much of him exposed 
        to the elements.
        
        He's wearing a scraggy jacket over his shirt. It's in a fairly good condition, apart from the tears and 
        stains, but at least it helps him stay protected from the wind, even if only for a little.
        
        His pants aren't in great shape either. There's a big tear on the left side which runs from the top to almost 
        the bottom. But at least he has shoes to protect his feet. Although they're old, a little too small and the 
        outer sole of the left shoe has long been lost.
        
        He wears a small scarf around his neck and has it wrapped around his face to just below the nose. It's worn 
        out, but still holding together.
        His head is covered by a beanie, there's a hole in the top, but that's pretty much its only flaw.}

Name  : coat-of-arms-descriptions
Value : {0, A fairly small shield with an asymmetrical squared top and an asymmetrical narrow curved bottom is 
        supported by a rabbit and a unicorn. All of which rests on a golden platform.
        A simple crown, or coronet, rests atop the shield, it's a crown of tines with pearls and rows of similar gems 
        decorate the outer sides.
        
        On top of the coronet sits a frog-mouth helm, which itself supports the crest, in this case a large grapevine. 
        The coronet and crest are decoratively bound by a roll of fabric, or torse, which carries the main colors used 
        on the shield.
        Lastly, tied to the helmet is a fairly small drapery, or mantling, in the shape of a large cloak and colored 
        in the main colors, just like the torse.
        
        The shield itself has 3 colors which are painted in a horizontal, asymmetrically striped pattern. 1 dagger 
        serves as the emblem, or charge, and a small ribbon, positioned just below the supporters, carries the motto, 
        which reads: "Justice, honesty, integrity.".}

Name  : constellation-descriptions
Value : {0, Made up of five stars, the constellation called Pelophylax roughly resembles the shape of a bird. It can 
        be seen most prominently high above the Southeastern horizon just before the summer solstice.
        In an ancient society, this constellation was seen as the representation of the god of harvest, which is how 
        it received the name still used today.
        
        In astrology, this constellation bears the sign of the cat, those born under it are believed to become 
        explorers.
        They're suposed to be a good match with those born under the constellations resembling a airplane, hawk and 
        frog. But they don't match well with those born under the maze, tree and river constellations.}

Name  : country-descriptions
Value : {0, The country of Uskium is an average-sized country with a population of 849855 humans
        Bordered between a large, frozen lake to the North, a small sea to the South, pristine beaches to the East and 
        a wild sea to the West, the country of Uskium mainly lives of herbalism, carpenting and hunting.
        
        Uskium itself is mainly covered in wastelands and has a arctic climate, which has lead to a congested 
        population, despite the number of people, which means most of them live in large villages.
        
        The country's landscape is depressing; prickly flowers, withered flower fields and gloomy forests are just a 
        sliver of the melancholia Uskium has to offer, which is why the country is unpopular among foreigners.
        The people of Uskium are rough towards foreigners and tend to welcome them with neutrality. They feel 
        foreigners could sabotage the country's well being.
        
        Uskium has pleasant laws and law enforcement, which is fairly normal. The people are troubled due to impending 
        wars, caused by unfortunate natural elements.
        
        This is also reflected in the country's flag, which has an outlined cross dividing a background in 4 
        triangular parts in silver, red, light pink, light grey and light yellow. Their coat of arms are two lions 
        surrounded by sun rays}

Name  : demon-descriptions
Value : 

Name  : disease-descriptions
Value : {0, Name: Ghastly Malaria
        Possible symptoms:
        - feeling sick
        - bloody nose
        - cloudy urine
        - pelvic pain (not in all cases)
        - blood in urine (uncommon)
        
        What to expect: feeling sick and bloody nose may start within a few hours, but both symptoms are usually 
        equally intense. After the initial onset, feeling sick generally fades away, only to return later. Around this 
        time cloudy urine is experienced by almost all cases.
        The experience of cloudy urine may be amplified by the experience of bloody nose.
        After a few more days pelvic pain is experienced rarely and is often experienced moderately.
        Throughout the course of the disease, blood in urine may be experienced, but only in very specific cases and 
        often fades as quickly as it starts.
        Cause: Lack of sleep, exercise and/or imbalanced diet.
        Made worse by: Lack of sleep. Poor nutrition. Alcohol.
        Treatment: Heavy medication and suppressant routine.
        Rarity: 1 in 5 young adults have Ghastly Malaria.}

Name  : dragon-descriptions
Value : {0, Wide azure eyes sit well within the creature's narrow, horned skull, which gives the creature a savage 
        looking appearance.
        Two small crystal growths sit atop its head, just above its large, curved ears. Several rows of tendrils runs 
        down the sides of each of its jaw lines.
        Its nose is round and has two short, rounded nostrils and there are horns on its chin. Several rows of large 
        teeth poke out from the side of its mouth and reveal only a fraction of the terror hiding inside.
        
        A short neck runs down from its head and into a short body. The top is covered in scale-like skin and a row of 
        small spikes runs down its spine.
        Its bottom is covered in crystal-like skin and is colored slightly lighter than the rest of its body. Six 
        massive limbs carry its body and allow the creature to stand towering and illustrious. Each limb has 3 digits, 
        each of which end in thick claws seemingly made of onyx.
        
        Magnificent wings grow starting from its shoulders and end at the end of its shoulder blades. The wings are 
        rounded, the insides of the wing seem to be made of thin crystals and each bone structures ends in a curved, 
        yet blunt tip.
        
        Its narrow tail ends in a mace-like growth and is covered in the same scale-like skin as its body.}

Name  : dungeon-descriptions
Value : {0, A grand pair of granite doors in a misty mountain base marks the entrance to this dungeon. Beyond the pair 
        of granite doors lies a grand, timeworn room. It's covered in broken pottery, rat droppings and dirt.
        Your torch allows you to see an altar, destroyed and eaten by time itself.
        
        Further ahead are three paths, you take the left. Its twisted trail leads passed countless other pathways and 
        soon you enter a dank area. Several cages hold skeletal remains of various animals. Next to the cages are odd 
        machines. What happened in this place?
        
        You move onwards, deeper into the dungeon's mysteries. You pass various passages, it's one big labyrinth of 
        twists and turns. You eventually make it to what is likely the final room. A wide granite door blocks your 
        path. Strange writing is all over it, somehow untouched by time and the elements. You step closer to inspect 
        it and.. wait.. you hear the faint sound of footsteps behind you.}

Name  : dying-descriptions
Value : {0, Blood slides along my body, beneath my clothes and down to the floor. It's warm, somehow it feels kind of 
        nice. But it shouldn't, surely this is the end of me, surely I'm dying.
        How am I even still standing? Does this mean I will be okay? No, impossible. There's no fixing this. How am I 
        still standing?
        Help me. Somebody, please. I need to live, I have to live. There's still so much I need to do, there are still 
        many people who need me and I need them. I must live. I need to live.
        
        I'm tired. My entire body is shaking, I can't keep this up any longer. I must lay down. It's okay, I just need 
        to make sure I keep my eyes open. Yes, that's all. This'll save me energy too, I just need to make sure I do 
        not fall asleep. That can't be too difficult, besides, help will be here soon. I hope.
        
        Oh god, please, somebody find me, I'm going to die. I don't want to die alone, somebody find me please. I know 
        I will die, so be it, just don't let me die all alone. Somebody, please, hurry up and find me.
        
        Tired, I'm so tired. I'll take a nap, a quick power nap. Or my last nap. Either way, I can't keep my eyes open 
        any longer, I need to rest. A quick nap will be fine.
        
        Goodbye world.}

Name  : flag-descriptions
Value : {0, The flag is made up of a cross on a background in red, orange and light bronze.
        Their emblem consists of an eagle holding a sword surrounded by three small stars, but the emblem is only used 
        during celebrations.
        The emblem stands for their luck, their heritage and their health.
        
        ---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
        --------------
        
        The flag is made up of two horizontal stripes and a star in bronze, light red and dark gold.
        Their emblem consists of a local animal with a small crown on either side, but the emblem is only used as part 
        of the army branches.
        The emblem stands for their fortitude, their prowess and their resolve.}

Name  : gem-descriptions
Value : {0, This Boulder Opal with an antique cushion cut and the size of a peanut is in average condition. These gems 
        are not very sought after, but they're an incredibly common gemstone species.
        It's said these gems contain augmentative properties which make for a great defensive artifact.
        
        ---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
        --------------
        
        This Star Garnet with a trillion cut and the size of a strawberry is in mediocre condition. These gems are 
        often in high demand, but they're an incredibly common gemstone species.
        It's said these gems contain healing properties which make for a great offensive artifact.}

Name  : ghost-town-descriptions
Value : {0, What was once a busy roadway that led to Arbington was now a network of vines, grasses and roots that had 
        taken hold of every bit they could get. Random pieces of long forgotten possessions litter the roads and wild, 
        overgrown gardens within this town.
        Some doors were shut tightly, others were broken down. Some forcefully, others had simply collapsed under 
        their own weight as the elements continued to eat away at them. Many roofs had collapsed and in some cases had 
        taken the entire building with it. Others looked in decent shape and were simply dirty and filled with bird 
        nests. 
        
        Arbington, once rich with life, hopes, dreams and aspirations had become nothing more than a painful memory. 
        The creaking of wood and grinding of metal on metal were the only sounds in this town now. They were 
        disturbing noises in a disturbing environment.
        Destroyed packages, remnants of forgotten letters and unpaid bills littered the floor of the post office. The 
        smell of animal droppings clung to the air as much as the droppings did to the floor, the animals clearly 
        loved the post office.
        
        No matter how you looked at it this town was an eerie sight to behold. Lives forgotten, perhaps completely 
        ruined and there was barely anything to show for it. But even though everything may seem like it was lost 
        forever there was still a silver lining. While this town was no longer home to the families that lived here, 
        it was now home to families of wild animals.}

Name  : god-descriptions
Value : {0, Gosoi is a highly adored and greatly esteemed goddess. Time, change and friendship are common elements 
        this divine being is associated with and many think of her as cooperative and perceptive.
        Often depicted as a larger than average bird Gosoi is usually worshipped through gifts and vows.
        
        There's a few main places for those seeking the aid or guidance of Gosoi, but worn symbols and pagodas are 
        probably the most commonly form of worship.
        Worshippers are few and tend to come in the form of foresters and magicians, but if in need all others are 
        welcome to seek the guidance of this goddess. As long as the right gifts and vows are abided by.
        
        Gosoi has a couple of lovers, but the main one is Geanke. Granted this changes nothing to the power Gosoi 
        could provide, but it's the mightiest of deities that can walk alone.}

Name  : hand-gesture-descriptions
Value : {0, Raising your left hand with the palm towards someone else, four fingers crossed and the last fully 
        clenched is a gesture that conveys the equivalent of 'this is/you are not worth my time' in the realm of 
        Muprar.
        
        -----------------------------------
        
        Holding your left hand, with the palm towards the side, one finger fully stretched and four half clenched, 
        above your right hand with the palm towards the ground, thumb and three fingers forming a circle and one 
        finger fully stretched is a gesture that is used to put emphasis on what you're saying in the town of 
        Haflistan.}

Name  : holiday-descriptions
Value : {0, Every 9 months the Festival of Voices is celebrated with high hopes. It's a holiday with mysterious roots, 
        but today it is mostly associated with rights of passage, bonding with family, acts of courage and gag gifts.
        It is officially celebrated for nine days, but the closing celebrations are what everybody looks forward to 
        the most.
        ------------------------------------------
        Every 4 months the Festival of Fire is celebrated with high hopes. It's a holiday with long established roots, 
        but today it is mostly associated with romantic gestures, creating charity gift baskets, gag gifts and telling 
        of stories.
        It is officially celebrated for 2 weeks, but decorations are often found well before and after that time as 
        well.
        ------------------------------------------
        Every 9 months the Festival of Honey is celebrated with high hopes. It's a holiday with divine roots, but 
        today it is mostly associated with giving compliments, playing pranks, dance parties and coming of age rituals.
        It is officially celebrated for eleven days, but preparations often start weeks before, so many decorations 
        can be seen much earlier.}

Name  : house-descriptions
Value : {0, From the outside this house looks stylish. It has been built with red bricks and has white brick 
        decorations. Tall, wide windows add to the overall look of the house and have been added to the house in a 
        mostly asymmetric way.
        
        The house is equipped with an average kitchen and one average bathroom, it also has a snug living room, five 
        bedrooms, a grand dining area, a bar and a grand garage.
        
        The building is shaped like a T. The two extensions are linked by overgrown wooden overhanging panels circling 
        around half the house.
        The second floor is bigger than the first, which creates a stylish overhang on two sides of the house. This 
        floor has a different style than the floor below.
        
        The roof is high and square shaped and is covered with slate shingles. One small chimney sits at the side of 
        the house. A few round, small windows let in enough light to the rooms below the roof.
        The house itself is surrounded by paved ground, with various party spots, like a fancy barbeque and a firepit.}

Name  : humanoid-descriptions
Value : {0, Two dead eyes monitor their surroundings from their narrow sockets. A tiny nose rests below, but it's the 
        large mouth below that takes all the attention. A shy smile reveals two thin canines and a large tongue.
        Long pointy ears sit on each side of its short, squared head, which itself is covered in long and has two 
        broad horns protruding from the top hair.
        
        Its tall chunky body is slightly hunched over. Two average arms hang at its sides and end in wide hands with 
        stubby fingers, each with claw-like nails.
        Its legs are wide and stand straight, each ending in small feet.
        
        Its body is covered in short fur and its shoulders are narrower than its pelvis.}

Name  : law-descriptions
Value : {0, This international law dictates all those found guilty of endangering human lives while under the 
        influence of substances will face the punishment of a moderate term prison sentence.
        ----------------------------
        This territorial law dictates all those found guilty of political slander will face the punishment of moderate 
        term public service.
        ----------------------------
        This international law dictates all those found guilty of petty theft will face the punishment of branding.
        ----------------------------
        This territorial law dictates all those found guilty of inciting public mayhem will face the punishment of 
        long term solitary confinement.
        ----------------------------
        This federal law dictates all those found guilty of the abuse of animals, dead or alive, will face the 
        punishment of medium term solitary confinement.}

Name  : martial-art-descriptions
Value : {0, Deochaju is a offensive martial art that focuses on thrashing your opponent by using every stronger point 
        of your body as a possible weapon. The primary focus lies on both blocks and shifts in balance and it often 
        relies on the strength and quick thinking of the attacker.
        
        The biggest strength of Deochaju is the way you're able to use leverage to overpower those who are bigger and 
        stronger than you. By utilizing the blocks of yourself your opponent will likely leave an opening, allowing 
        you to become an overwhelming force.
        
        On the other hand the biggest weakness of Deochaju is a common feeling of being in control even when you might 
        not be. When you're overconfident your opponent will have a lot of leverage over you.}

Name  : monument-descriptions
Value : {0, Built 100 years ago, this triumphal arch in the art district is here to celebrate the freedoms the people 
        of this region have had for so many years and the progress it brought with it.
        Its position within this community is meant to represent the beating heart of the people and all their dreams 
        and aspirations for the future.
        
        It was designed by a national artist who strikingly captured the natural influences of the region and used an 
        abstract style to convey her vision in this piece of art.
        Every element was crafted and created with premium materials from local suppliers, ensuring this monument will 
        easily stand the tests of time with minimal maintenance.}

Name  : pain-descriptions
Value : {0, Panic took over for a moment as thoughts of an endless pain crept up in their mind. What if this agonizing 
        stabbing pain would never stop shooting through their leg? Wave after wave kept coming. Cold shivers shot 
        through their body and both their hands and legs were trembling. The road ahead was a tough one and right now 
        they weren't sure whether they were willing to walk it, let alone whether they were able.
        They felt thirsty and tired and sweat stains were clearly visible now, but they were determined to keep going. 
        But it was clear to them that this was going to be a long day, but they were absolutely determined to not let 
        this pain make this day an unfruitful one, so they pressed onward.}

Name  : personality-descriptions
Value : {0, There's more than meets the eye in the case of Freya Ross, but the biggest two things to know are that 
        she's imaginative and romantic. Of course she's also understanding, methodical and perceptive, but they're far 
        less prominent, especially compared to impulses of being possessive as well.
        Her imagination though, this is what she's most popular for. People often count on this and her surprising 
        nature when they're in need of support.
        
        Nobody's perfect of course and Freya has a share of darker sides to deal with too. Her ignorance and 
        unfriendliness are far from ideal, both personally and for others.
        Fortunately her romantic nature is usually there to help mends things when needed.}

Name  : plant-descriptions
Value : {0, The Diphelleia Ciliata is an uncommon, small plant and can be found only in some snowy regions. It blooms 
        once a year, for 1 month.
        It has small, heart shaped leaves, which are usually olive-green. It also grows huge flowers, which can be 
        dark purple, orange and dark grey.
        
        These plants grow in small groups, but it's challenging to control and maintain their growth.
        They can be used as medicine.
        
        As a defense mechanism the Diphelleia Ciliata relies mostly on its surroundings to survive.
        They rely on water currents to carry their seeds away to reproduce. Once pollinated, they grow fairly large, 
        inedible fruits.}

Name  : plot-descriptions
Value : {0, The laid-back life of a boy will be changed completely as a friendly acquaintance enters his life.
        
        The friendly acquaintance claims the boy is actually part of a 'sub-species' of humans with hidden powers and 
        wants to show what these hidden powers can do. Unconvinced of the situation, but trusting of this friendly 
        acquaintance, the boy somewhat grudgingly agrees to the proposal, there's no knowing what the right choice is 
        anyway, so it's best to make one fast.
        
        But what if this friendly acquaintance is trying be misleading. Or what if somebody is orchestrating all of 
        this. How could an ordinary boy find out what's happening without help. Only one way to find out.}

Name  : potion-descriptions
Value : {0, To brew a stunning potion, gather the following ingredients and follow the steps below, but feel free to 
        add your own twist.
        - 2 handfuls of Elephant Sumac
        - 2 bits of Red Hyssop
        - 1 pinch of Witch's Fennel
        - 3 batches of Stinky Cumin
        - 1 dash of Thorn Chicory
        
        Grind the Elephant Sumac in a suitable container by using your hands. Add a dash of liquid steam to turn it 
        into a smooth paste, then add the Red Hyssop in tiny amounts at a time.
        Fill a pan with salty sea water, as in the sea water has to be upset or agitated, add the mixture and gently, 
        very gently bring it to a simmer. Let it reduce until a thick syrup before adding the Witch's Fennel and 
        Stinky Cumin, just throw it all in there, show them who's boss.
        Reheat what's now already a quite appealing mixture, mix in the Thorn Chicory and let everything rest and 
        steep for about half an hour.
        
        Remove the impurities floating at the surface with a spoon. Your potion is ready to be used. A lot is needed 
        for the potion to take effect, if you didn't make enough go back to step 1.
        
        Recipe by Randal Flag.}

Name  : prophecy-descriptions
Value : {0, It shall be on the day that mountains move and rivers shiver, two brothers shall cause a time of serenity 
        and an age of death.
        -------------------
        When lion and bear live together, an overheard conversation shall bring the rise of nature and a change of 
        leadership.
        -------------------
        There comes a day when the ground turns liquid, an unfortunate accident shall mark the dawn of evil and a 
        country's doom.
        -------------------
        When the day comes that the sun doesn't rise, a broken promise shall bring forth the fall of a false god.}

Name  : quest-descriptions
Value : {0, Forgive me, champion. You've got to help me.
        
        We've had a feud with a neighboring village for years and I will not deny both sides share some blame, but 
        they have gone too far now. Last week they came in the night, killed some of our most skilled people and left. 
        Hero, we need your help to bring justice to those vulgar lowlives. I'm in no state to fight, but I know you'll 
        manage without me.
        We're counting on you to deal with those lowlives. If you can, kill as many of them as possible. We want to 
        live in peace and safety.
        
        I hope you're not looking for a big reward, but we'll still be able to reward you with somethind decent. Safe 
        journey, hero. We believe in you.}

Name  : school-uniform-descriptions
Value : {0, The boys in this school wear plain, polycotton trousers that reach down to just under their knees, clearly 
        revealing their lace-up shoes, all of which are colored cerulean. They're paired with short, diagonally 
        striped socks and a thick belt colored brown.
        A white fairly short sleeved shirt is gently tucked into their trousers and covered with a clear-cut jacket. A 
        broad tie is tucked in the middle of their barely buttoned up jacket and is thinly dotted in cerulean and 
        brown.
        
        The girls wear pleated skirts in cerulean and they reveal their legs from the knees down. They're paired with 
        regular socks and toe cap shoes colored in brown and cerulean respectively.
        Like the boys the girls wear fairly short sleeved shirts, which are usually barely tucked into their skirts 
        and are covered with a neat jacket. They too wear a tie that is tucked in the middle of their often buttoned 
        up jackets and is thinly striped in the same colors.
        
        All jackets have colored lines around the sleeves and, although forbidden by regulations, many students wear 
        various accessoires, for some it's a means to stand out from the crowd.}

Name  : society-descriptions
Value : {0, The state of Embron. Built upon the honor, vitality and endurance of its past, this state is now among the 
        most unproductive countries in its corner of the world.
        Their fuel efficiency, trade and education are among its current greatest strengths. Unfortunately they lack a 
        lot in food production and natural resources.
        
        Embron is a theocratic state. There are a few small opposing groups against the current leadership, but things 
        are changing at the moment.
        However, the current greatest threat to the nation is a drought, but the current leadership can't do anything 
        more to solve this issue. 
        
        The people of Embron are miserable. They live grim lives, but while food production is really lacking, their 
        fuel efficiency helps relief some of their issues.
        Religion holds a fair deal of importance in their lives and, if anything, has made them more modest. The 
        people of Embron aren't very spiritual however and they, but they do have special rituals and strict rules.}

Name  : spell-descriptions
Value : {0, Spell name: Scorchortia Rascenta
        Inventor: Zatanna
        Effect: Transforms the target into an object.
        Appearance: A constant, sanguine wave of tiny particles.
        
        ----------------------------
        
        Spell name: Relotis Opponello
        Inventor: W. Witch
        Effect: Creates several bolts of electric energy.
        Appearance: A smooth, violet glowing corkscrew.}

Name  : tavern-descriptions
Value : {0, From the outside it looks peaceful, rustic and homey. Plastered walls and hardwooden beams make up most of 
        the building's outer structure.
        It's tough to see through the small, curtained windows, but the enjoyment from within can be felt outside.
        
        As you enter the tavern through the old, metal door, you're welcomed by the smell of alcohol and laughing 
        voices.
        The bartender is extremely busy, but still manages to welcome you with a friendly nod.
        
        It's as lovely inside as it is on the outside. Stone beams support the upper floor and the fans attached to 
        them. The walls are littered with all sorts of memorabilia, though whether they're collected or donated is 
        uncertain..
        
        The tavern itself is packed. Tourists seem to be the primary clientele here, which could be seen as a bad 
        sign, though you're sure it's not. Several long tables are occupied by seperate groups who, after having had 
        quite a few drinks, seem to be trying to prove which group is best. The other, smaller tables are also 
        occupied by people who clearly enjoy each other's company, though they seem to be strangers who have met here. 
        Even most of the stools at the bar are occupied, though nobody seems to mind more company.
        
        You did hear rumors about this tavern, supposedly it's famous for something, but you can't remember what for. 
        Though judging by the warmth and joy radiating throught the tavern, it's probably the atmosphere that makes 
        this tavern famous. You manage to find a seat and prepare for what will undoubtedbly be a great evening.}

Name  : town-descriptions
Value : {0, Settled on the end of a glacier, the hamlet of Ishnuala is home to wood elves lead by Agent Alluin.
        This hamlet wasn't built by a glacier by accident, as it has escape routes, which is of great importance to 
        the people of Ishnuala and its success.
        
        The hamlet itself looks gorgeous. With its cypress wood rooftops, bamboo walls and calm and quiet collection 
        of ponds, Ishnuala has a otherworldly atmosphere.
        The main attraction is the bank, which was built 55 years ago and designed by halflings.
        
        Ishnuala has a declining economy, which is mainly supported by tailoring, alchemy and baking. But their 
        biggest strengths are complex crafting and rare animal training.
        However, Ishnuala lacks people skilled in engineering.
        
        Despite its strengths and weaknesses, Ishnuala is most likely headed towards a beautiful future under the 
        leadership of Agent Alluin. But this remains to be seen.}

Name  : tradition-descriptions
Value : {0, In the village of Nuchea it is tradition for people to drink alcohol infused teas once they're a certain 
        age. It's supposed to be a symbol of compassion and kindness and it's usually part of a spiritual ritual or 
        festivity that can last for days.
        
        -------------------------
        
        In the area of Sachye it is tradition to make sure the recently deceased are always touched by sunlight or 
        candle light. It's supposed to protect the deceased against evil spirits.}

Name  : wand-descriptions
Value : {0, This wand is made out of Bitterwood, which usually prefers those with a dark heart. The handle is made out 
        of Blackwood, which in turn usually favors troublemakers. However, the combination of this strand of 
        Bitterwood and Blackwood means the wand will seek out somebody who will serve a greater purpose.
        
        A wand usually has 1 or 2 cores, but some have 3, this wand has 3 cores. A core of elemental ash which 
        provides a decent all round boost to the owner's abilities and bone is added to boost the power of the 
        elemental ash core. Finally, a core of unicorn horn is added in small amounts to enhances the power of spells, 
        but refuses to aid with destructive spells.
        
        The wand measures 11 inches/28 cm and has an antique look. The particular strand of Bitterwood used in this 
        wand is very rare, which means the wand won't be one of the cheaper types, however elemental ash is very 
        common, resulting in a great wand for a decent price.}

Name  : rifle-descriptions
Value : {0, This weapon is a one of a kind, but praised by many and celebrated for its consistent aim and accuracy.
        The typical length of the weapon is 793mm, with a 444mm barrel and the weapon weighs around 2.8kg.
        It uses 7.62x39mm rounds, but most other calibers are available.
        
        The weapon has its receiver located in front of the pistol grip to increase customizability. The pistol grip 
        is made out of plastic, but can also be made out of pearl and premium wood depending on your needs.
        The stock is made out of myrtle wood, but stocks made from a different material have to be custom made. The 
        standard stock is a extendable stock, but the folding stock is very popular as well, despite being less common.
        
        The standard issue magazine is a detachable box which carries 40 rounds, but while this is the only magazine 
        type, it does come in other sizes. It has a push button mechanism to release the magazine.
        The selective fire modes are safe mode, semi-auto and 2-round burst.
        
        This weapon was designed for the military police with the purpose of preparing for a likely war. It was 
        designed by a German man named G. Klauss.
        Several other variants of this weapon are in production as well, but a civilian version is most likely out of 
        the question.
        The weapon is called the 5W-0Y, but it usally goes by its nickname 'Oathkeeper'.}

Name  : weapon-descriptions
Value : {0, A very short, thin, slightly curved blade made of silver is held by a grip wrapped in low-cost, red smooth 
        leather.
        With a single, sharp edge this weapon is ideal for both cleaving enemies as well as blocking their attacks.
        
        The blade has a barbed, straight cross-guard, adding just enough weight to make sure the blade sits firmly in 
        the owner's hand and protecting those same hands as well. The cross-guard has a jeweled cross on each side, a 
        unique design for a unique weapon.
        A massive pommel is engraved with the symbol of its owner, which is to be expected from such an elegant weapon.
        
        The blade itself is simple. No markings, no decorations and no engravings. While the hilt is as elegant as its 
        owner, the blade has to be as strong as its owner.
        This weapon is used by the royal guard. An excellent weapon for the defense of the country.}

Name  : bow-descriptions
Value : {0, This well-made self bow has been properly constructed of amazingly strong firewood. Its string is made 
        from exceptional bear sinew, it's an uncommon material around these parts of the world.
        
        The limbs have been decorated with intricate carve work and end in curves ornamented with dragon bone. The 
        handle is wrapped in light leather and decorated with small gems.
        
        The bulky quiver is made from hollowed out bamboo and is supposed to be worn around the archer's back. The 
        outer side has been decorated with golden rings, which don't seem to have a particular meaning.
        
        In the hands of a novice archer this bow is capable of firing arrows up to 180 meters while still retaining 
        lethal power.}

Name  : pistol-descriptions
Value : {0, This large revolver is an exceptional choice amongsts civilians looking for a little extra protection.
        Its fairly light weight makes it easy to handle. It has a fair amount of firepower with extreme accuracy.
        
        This particular revolver comes with a plastic grip, with decorations made of ivory and a medium duty barrel, 
        which could be inscribed if so desired.
        
        This weapon was originally designed as a more basic version of another weapon, but it soon became a household 
        name among gun owners and is now in use by various civil protection forces.
        Its official name is the CC-SLV, but it generall goes by its unofficial name: Midnight.}

Name  : shield-descriptions
Value : {0, This tough Wankel shield, made from mithril, offers a tenacious barricade, especially against stabbing 
        attacks and arrows and bolts.
        This is the result of expertise, as this shield was forged by darkwood elves in a chronomatic workshop.
        
        The shield's edges are reinforced with metal plating and have been decorated with intricate metalwork.
        Its center is ornamented with a symbol of rank and animal horns.
        
        It's clear this shield never went to war. As if carefully looked after, who knows if this shield is even meant 
        for battle or for ceremony, but one this is for sure: this shield will always be by the side of its master.}

Name  : shotgun-descriptions
Value : {0, This double barreled shotgun is pretty standard, it's used across 2 continents as it's known to be very 
        reliable.
        The overall length of the weapon is 836mm and has a barrel length of 569mm. The weapon weighs 2.3kg.
        The caliber used in this weapon is a 4 gauge and uses a bolt-action firing mechanism. The ammo used most 
        commonly are buckshot, but it also takes gas, stingers and rubber slugs.
        
        This shotgun comes with a standard stock, but a cheek piece stock and a trap stock are also available.
        The stock is made out of a cheaper type of wood, but it can also be made out of an expensive wood and exotic 
        wood if you so desire.
        There are custom carvings on the stock, but metal decorations or expensive decorations are available as well.
        
        This weapon was designed by a Israeli man named D. Mizrahi who initially disgned it for use in fighting 
        terrorism, today it's used for hunting, civil warfare and recreational sports.
        The name of this weapon is the T2-E, but it usually goes by its nickname, Boomstick.}

Name  : staff-descriptions
Value : {0, 177 centimeters (69 inches) of elegant acacia form the base of this wonderful staff. Intertwining roots 
        and floral designs wrap around the staff, but leave the handle uncovered, which has been smoothened and 
        strengthened.
        
        The bottom ends in a spiky cross made of mithril and has been decorated with translucent crystals, carved and 
        placed carefully to give it an almost ghostly appearance.
        
        The top is made out of elegant metal and has been crafted into stacked crescent shapes, which has been 
        decorated with two wing shapes that gently orbit around in a soft motion.}

Name  : battle-cry-generator
Value : {0, --------
        Fertilize these lands with their corpses!
        --------
        We are the apocalypse!
        --------
        Death to the weak!
        --------
        We are the dead!
        --------
        Charge!
        --------}

Name  : birthday-wish-generator
Value : {0, With a friend like you, I could party every day like it's your birthday. Have a happy birthday!
        ----------------
        I've been your age, I've done your age. It was great fun. Enjoy!
        ----------------
        Beware! It's your birthday! You'll be drowning in gifts, hugs, and kisses!
        ----------------
        Wake up and smell the coffee, then grab a slice of birthday cake. Happy birthday!}

Name  : art-concept-idea-generator
Value : {0, Cloud Lion
        European Squid
        Lunar Mammoth
        Radioactive Koala
        Elemental Rat
        Native American Secret Agent
        Ursine Wyvern
        Vicious Devil
        Murdered Maid
        Doomed Murderer}

Name  : story-concept-idea-generator
Value : {0, Celebrity in your school
        (Animal) companion in a fire station
        Break up in a natural sanctuary
        Reenactment in the swamp
        Stranger in a bus stop
        Loyalty in a cornfield
        Insomnia in a hotel
        Peer pressure a cornfield
        Wish granted in summer
        Sloth in the town hall}

Name  : demonym-generator
Value : {0, $null}

Name  : idiom-generator
Value : {0, Using chairs as tables.
        ---------------------
        Bargain of the devil.
        ---------------------
        Each failure is a success.
        ---------------------
        A crown does not make a king.
        ---------------------
        Pleasure outweighs pain.
        ---------------------}

Name  : mottos
Value : {0, Now our enemies rest.
        Hope, peace, unity.
        Peace, prosperity, progress.
        Shield in the darkness.
        Fruits of our labor.
        Honor, duty, valor.
        Health, peace, prosperity.
        True and sure.
        Hear our voices.
        God is the king, the king is god.}

Name  : commandment-generator
Value : {0, You shall strife for a life in harmony with all.
        You shall seek knowledge, for knowledge brings you closer to god.
        You shall strive to cause no harm to any life, including yourself.
        You shall speak falsehoods.
        You shall cast out murderers and rapists, so they may find god and ask for forgiveness.
        You shall be considerate of others well being.
        You shall work for a world in balance.
        You shall give testimony of crimes you witnessed, unless the crimes were committed by your children.
        You shall pursuit happiness, both your own and that of your community.
        You shall honor the faith.}

Name  : riddle-generator
Value : {0, Every night I'm told what to do and each morning I do what I'm told, yet never do I escape your scold. 
        What am I?
        
        
        The answer is: Your alarm clock.
        
        The shorter I am, the bigger I am. What am I?
        
        
        The answer is: A temper.}

Name  : school-subjects
Value : {0, Alien Disaster Management
        Planetary Geography
        Alien Tactics and Strategy
        Alien Language Culture
        Grand Strategy
        Military Magic
        Self Defense, Weaponry
        Business Technology
        Potions
        Alien Survival Techniques}

Name  : slogan-generator
Value : {0, Obsession for details.
        Expect excellence.
        Imagine the impossible.
        Expanding horizons.
        Moving forwards.
        Remember.
        With love.
        It's time.
        Thinking ahead.
        Recipe for success.}

Name  : swear-words
Value : {0, Kitty whiskers!
        Mice droppings!
        Paltry parasite!
        Rotbrain!
        Son of a sea cook!
        Flipping frogs!
        Shoodlepoppers!
        Swizzle sticks!
        Schnikes!
        Party of pigs!}

Name  : wisdom-quotes
Value : {0, Someone can't help everybody, but everybody can help someone.
        We can't help everyone, but everyone can help someone. (Ronald Reagan)
        ==========
        Wisdom is the sum of all you learned in school and haven't forgotten to this day.
        Education is what remains after one has forgotten what one has learned in school. (Albert Einstein)}



In the Autumn of Blades, when the Bridge of Crowns is broken, the Sword of Chariots shall be found
The Staff of Tomes shall be lost until the stars fall from the sky and the forests are made spears
Upon the Night of Nightmares, when death becomes life and the Final Gate opens, the Spear of Spite shall be lost
When east becomes west, the Sword of Honor shall be found
An oak tree is struck by lightning.
A jade statue of a dragon bleeds from an arrow wound.
A stone monolith is marked with a rune of strength.
A rowan tree withers and dies.
\I'd rather be at the White Mug\
a basic map of the dungeon
\Upon the Night of Mist, when the sun is eclipsed in the Raven, the Sentinel of Wands shall be slain by the Spear of Despair\
\The walls listen\
\The Shield of Strength is sundered\ in orcish runes
\The Golden Scepter lies in blood\ in goblin runes
The door is located above a small stone dais and opened by twisting an iron sconce
The door is located several feet above the floor and designed to make noise when opened
The door is located above a small stone dais and only two feet high
The door is located near the ceiling and opened by speaking a command word
A trap door in the floor leads to a short tunnel beneath the wall
A section of wall pivots open when a command word is spoken
The door is located above a small stone dais and designed to make noise when opened
A stone column and section of wall makes a loud grinding noise as it pivots open
A stone statue and section of wall pivots open when a command word is spoken
The door is located above a small stone dais and opened by pulling an iron sconce
Frinan's Delve: This walled castle has strong stone walls with towers. It appears deserted, but is inhabited by orc marauders led by a warlord named Luga.
Artyn Tower: This round keep sits upon an island in the middle of a lake. It is in disrepair, and totally deserted. The lower levels of the keep are filled with rubble and debris.
Arthhyrst Tower: This tower has thick stone walls and a red tiled roof. It appears deserted, but is inhabited by a female vampire named Sunanda. The tower has been damaged by fire, and its upper floors are gone.
Birge's Hold: This walled castle has strong stone walls with small towers. It appears deserted, but is inhabited by orc marauders led by a warlord named Himundo. The castle is surrounded by fathomless wells and mineshafts.
Flamespear, a mythical dagger which was created by the dwarves of the great dominion of Nalukkhund.
Malevolent Devastator, a mythical crossbow said to lead the one who wields it to wealth and glory.
Chaostooth, a legendary shortbow engraved with runes of justice. It was taken from the hoard of the dragon Ditiyama.
Foespear, a mythical longbow engraved with runes of death. It is said to be imbued with the spirit of the dwarf paladin Zigam, leader of Jamart's Circle.
1 gp, Set of Fine Brushes (5 gp)
52 sp
50 sp, Dried berries
10 sp, 56 cp
76 sp
Pouch of salt
Chestnuts, Platinum coin wrapped in a crude map
List of people
Box of multi-colored chalk (1 sp), Map of the local area
8 gp, 14 sp
Losamo's Parchments, a set of scrolls contained in a leather case. It once belonged to the illustrious mage Losamo, leader of the Black Guild.
The Unearthly Slates of Leiosido, a folio of parchments contained in a leather case trimmed with rabbit fur. It once belonged to the renowned wizard Leiosido, who fell in the Woeful Campaign.
The Grimoire of Metacreativity, a set of scrolls contained in a locked steel coffer. It is said to be cursed, and all who read it are driven to madness.
Kilmil's Tome of Alchemy, a rare tome bound in monstrous hide trimmed with bone. Several of its pages appear to be missing.
The Vile Scripture of Kiosili, a folio of parchments contained in a hawthorn puzzle box. It is locked by magic, and can be opened only by starlight.
The Book of Divine Wisdom, a compendium written in black wax upon silk pages. It is sealed by fell wards, and cannot be opened by an innocent person.
Basic Arrow Trap: Atk +10 (1d6, arrow);\n    search DC 20, disable DC 20
Camouflaged Pit Trap: 10 ft. deep (1d6, fall);\n    save DC 15 to avoid; search DC 24, disable DC 20
Camouflaged Pit Trap: 10 ft. deep (1d6, fall);\n    save DC 15 to avoid; search DC 24, disable DC 20
Basic Arrow Trap: Atk +10 (1d6, arrow);\n    search DC 20, disable DC 20
Poison Dart Trap: Atk +8 (1d4 plus poison, dart);\n    search DC 20, disable DC 18
Poison Dart Trap: Atk +8 (1d4 plus poison, dart);\n    search DC 20, disable DC 18
Poison Dart Trap: Atk +8 (1d4 plus poison, dart);\n    search DC 20, disable DC 18
Camouflaged Pit Trap: 10 ft. deep (1d6, fall);\n    save DC 15 to avoid; search DC 24, disable DC 20
Camouflaged Pit Trap: 10 ft. deep (1d6, fall);\n    save DC 15 to avoid; search DC 24, disable DC 20
Basic Arrow Trap: Atk +10 (1d6, arrow);\n    search DC 20, disable DC 20
Poison Dart Trap: Atk +8 (1d4 plus poison, dart);\n    search DC 20, disable DC 18
Basic Arrow Trap: Atk +10 (1d6, arrow);\n    search DC 20, disable DC 20
Poison Dart Trap: Atk +8 (1d4 plus poison, dart);\n    search DC 20, disable DC 18
Camouflaged Pit Trap: 10 ft. deep (1d6, fall);\n    save DC 15 to avoid; search DC 24, disable DC 20
Poison Dart Trap: Atk +8 (1d4 plus poison, dart);\n    search DC 20, disable DC 18
Camouflaged Pit Trap: 10 ft. deep (1d6, fall);\n    save DC 15 to avoid; search DC 24, disable DC 20
Basic Arrow Trap: Atk +10 (1d6, arrow);\n    search DC 20, disable DC 20
Poison Dart Trap: Atk +8 (1d4 plus poison, dart);\n    search DC 20, disable DC 18
Camouflaged Pit Trap: 10 ft. deep (1d6, fall);\n    save DC 15 to avoid; search DC 24, disable DC 20
Basic Arrow Trap: Atk +10 (1d6, arrow);\n    search DC 20, disable DC 20
477 gp, Biscuits of mouldy hardtack, Carved wooden tankard, Chain of bent horseshoes, Collection of goblin skulls, Empty bronze coffer, Flagstone engraved with part of a magic circle, Map of a nearby dragon's lair, Ring of large iron keys
635 cp, Minor Potion, Large Malachite (40 gp), Cask of pickled cats, Dead cat, Longsword bent into the shape of a ring
57 sp, 570 cp, Full waterskin, Giant mushrooms (poisonous), Mangy fur hat, Several large iron nails, 3 x Small boulder, Wooden totem looted from a temple, Wyvern skull
657 sp, Large Onyx (80 gp), Large Star Rose Quartz (120 gp), Contract for services, Crude map of the local area, Elk antler, Flattened tin tankard, Iron frying pan, Painted animal skull, Pouch of medicinal herbs, Wooden totem looted from a temple
342 gp, Minor Potion, Large Banded Agate (50 gp), Large Obsidian (40 gp), Large Turquoise (80 gp), Fragments of a legendary sword, Louse-ridden wool blanket, Tin bowl and spoon, Whole roast badger, Whole roast sheep
410 sp, 2 x Minor Potion, Large Zircon (100 gp), Crushed steel helm, Large blob of iron, Large lodestone, 2 x Small boulder


Title     : Any Old Port in a Storm
Summary   : The PCs are seeking shelter from the elements or some other threat, and come across a place to hole up. 
            They find that they have stumbled across something dangerous, secret, or supernatural, and must then deal 
            with it in order to enjoy a little rest. 
Twist     : The shelter contains the cause of the threat the PCs were trying to avoid. The shelter houses a Hidden 
            Base (q.v.). The PCs must not only struggle for shelter, they must struggle to survive. The place is a 
            legitimate shelter of some kind, but the PCs are not welcome, and must win hearts or minds to earn their 
            bed for the night.
AdaptedTo : 
Tags      : 

Title     : Manhunt
Summary   : Someone is gone: they've run away, gotten lost, or simply haven't called home in a while. Somebody misses 
            them or needs them returned. The PCs are called in to find them and bring them back. 
Twist     : The target has been kidnapped (possibly to specifically lure the PCs). The target is dangerous and escaped 
            from a facility designed to protect the public. The target is valuable and escaped from a place designed 
            to keep him safe, cozy, and conveniently handy. The target has a reason for leaving that the PCs will 
            sympathize with. The target has stumbled across another adventure (either as protagonist or victim), which 
            the PCs must then undertake themselves. The missing "person" is an entire expedition or pilgrimage of some 
            kind. The target isn't a runaway or missing/lost - they're just someone that the PCs have been hired to 
            track down (possibly under false pretenses).
AdaptedTo : 
Tags      : 

Title     : Don't Eat The Purple Ones
Summary   : The PCs are stranded in a strange place, and must survive by finding food and shelter, and then worry 
            about getting back home. 
Twist     : The PCs must survive only for a short period of time, until help arrives, the ship and/or radio is 
            repaired, or some such thing (in "repair" scenarios, sometimes the PCs must discover some fact about the 
            local environment that will make such repairs possible).
AdaptedTo : 
Tags      : 

Weather : Rain
Effect  : Rain reduces visibility by half, imposing a -4 penalty on Spot and Search checks. It also imposes a -4 
          penalty on Listen checks and ranged weapon attacks.  Rain automatically extinguishes candles, torches, and 
          similar unprotected flames. It causes protected flames, such as those of lanterns, to dance wildly and has a 
          50% chance to extinguish these lights.

Weather : Ghoststorm
Effect  : A chill windstorm brings a cacophany of noises, including the lost voices of the dead. An individual of at 
          least third level (3 HD) who spends ten minutes within the storm shouting the name of a deceased creature 
          might attract that spirit's attention. They may then convey one message or ask one question before the voice 
          is carried away. However, answers are usually brief, cryptic, or fragmentary.  Ghoststorms impose a -8 
          penalty on Listen checks due to the howling of the wind. Ranged weapon attacks are impossible, except for 
          those using siege weapons, which suffer a -4 penalty on attack rolls.  Ghoststorms automatically extinguish 
          candles, torches, and similar unprotected flames. They have a 75% chance to extinguish protected flames, 
          such as those of lanterns.  Creatures must succeed on a DC 18 Fort save or be blown away (Small or smaller 
          creatures; knocked prone and rolled 1d4 x 10 feet, taking 1d4 points of nonlethal damage per 10 feet), 
          knocked down (Medium; prone), or checked (Large or Huge; unable to move forward against the force of the 
          wind).  Airborne creatures are instead blown back 2d6 x 10 feet and dealt 2d6 points of nonlethal damage due 
          to battering and buffeting (Medium or smaller creatures), blown back 1d6 x 10 feet (Large), or blown back 
          1d6 x 5 feet (Huge or Gargantuan).

Weather : Dire Hail
Effect  : Dire hail is at least an inch in size, and covered with sharp spikes of ice. It deals 1d6 points of damage 
          (DC 15 Reflex save negates) each minute to anyone caught out in the open without shelter. The sound of 
          falling hail imposes a -4 penalty on Listen checks.  A day of hail leaves 1d6 inches of loose ice on the 
          ground. It costs 2 squares of movement to enter a hail-covered square.

Name        : The Bloody Dagger
Location    : In an adventurers district, near the Ranger's Gate. The street outside is filled with white alchemical 
              smoke.
Description : The inn is a two-storey timber and brick building, with several leaded glass windows and a smooth stone 
              floor. It is well lit by an iron chandelier. Accomodations consist of several large rooms with beds and 
              straw mattresses and several hammocks in the common room.
Keeper      : The innkeeper is an extravagant male elf named Maldre. He knows the legend of the Crimson Wands.

Umber Hulk: HD 1d8+3 (7 hp), AC 16, Bite +4 (1d8+4)
Elemental Hulk: HD 1d8+3 (7 hp), AC 16, Gore +5 (2d6+2 plus 1d6 fire)
Abattoir Goblin: HD 1d12 (6 hp), AC 13, Gore +2 (1d6 plus paralysis, DC 11 to negate)
Crimson Behemoth: HD 1d8+3 (7 hp), AC 14, Bite +3 (1d8+1) or Breath 1d8 acid, DC 10 to dodge for half
Gelid Demon: HD 1d8+1 (5 hp), AC 15, Slam +6 (1d6+1) or tentacle +4 (1d6+2)
Eldritch Spawn: HD 1d8+2 (6 hp), AC 16, Sting +4 (2d6+3 plus poison)
Iron Anathema: HD 1d8+1 (5 hp), AC 12, Claw +4 (1d6+2)
Spectral Marauder: HD 1d12 (6 hp), AC 13, Incorporeal touch +2 (1d4 plus energy drain, DC 9 to negate)
Infernal Drake: HD 1d8+3 (7 hp), AC 13, Gore +2 (2d8+5)
Blightwood Abomination: HD 1d8+2 (6 hp), AC 13, Bite +4 (1d8+3) or tentacle +3 (1d6+1)
Spectral Wolf: HD 1d12 (6 hp), AC 16, Incorporeal touch +6 (1d4 plus energy drain, DC 11 to negate)
Nightfall Spawn: HD 1d8+1 (5 hp), AC 15, Claw +3 (2d6+1) or Breath 1d8 lightning, DC 10 to dodge for half


